open-site.org 2018-05-10

# Open-Site | What are you interested in learning?

Thank you for your interest in using our website content and services. This document explains the conditions governing use of our website, and the way in which Open-Site.org gathers and applies different types of information in order to bring you content and related products and services. Your use of our website assumes you agree to these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

Generally we collect information in two categories:

  * Submitted information: We provide web forms for the voluntary submission of personal contact information including name, telephone number, mailing address and email address, in order to provide the services requested by our visitors, as well as any other information needed to match you to an education product or service. We collect your submitted information, store it and share it with schools and other third parties to provide you with information about schools, programs and education related services, as necessary. Your voluntary submission of this information authorizes Open-Site.org and our affiliated schools and partners to contact you by telephone, text messages, email or mail, in accordance with all applicable laws, regarding education options or related topics. Below you will find more information on this and other important topics. If you receive any email communications from us, a school, or third party and wish to unsubscribe, you will be afforded the ability through a link in the email to opt-out, at which point you will be removed from that sender’s further mailings.
  * Automatic information: Whenever you interact with us, we also receive and store certain types of anonymous information, as most websites do. Making improvements and creating a more relevant user experience are the primary ways in which we use this information. We use “cookies” to collect anonymous data, for example, for analytics, site optimization and for tailored advertising and marketing purposes. Examples of anonymous data include, but are not limited to, your browser version, operating system version, and your IP address. More information about our use of cookies can be found below in this document.

By utilizing our website, we assume you acknowledge and agree that information we collect on our website may be shared with schools, affiliated companies, and third parties, to provide you with degree information, as well as inform you of other programs and education related products and services. Additionally, you acknowledge and agree with our right to release any collected information, personally identifiable or otherwise, as needed, to businesses providing administration services to our company, for example: email service delivery. 

By submitting personal information to Open-Site.org, Your permission is granted for us, our affiliated entities, including schools, third party marketing partners and vendors to contact you, including via telephone, text messages, email, or mail to provide information, marketing or otherwise, for education related services and products. Additionally, this action grants us, our affiliates, and partners and vendors, the right to contact you and relinquish any rights granted to you by the Do Not Call list or other applicable law, for a period of time. Through your submission you effectively omit Do Not Call requirements established by state and federal governments and may also provide exemption for us from other applicable laws.

Through your submission you also allow us the right to release your personal information, for example to abide by a subpoena or other legal procedure, or in other instances required by law. We exercise this option when, in good faith, we believe it is necessary to preserve our rights, ensure the safety of you or others, explore alleged fraud, to reply to a government or legal request, and/or in the instance that Open-Site.org enters into a merger, acquisition, or sale of some or all of its assets to a third party.

### Terms of Use and Privacy Policy Changes Notification

It is possible we will perform revisions to our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy in the future if we change our practices, therefore we recommend that you reread this document periodically for the most up to date practices concerning your privacy and other important information.

### Cookie Policy

Using this website means you acknowledge and consent to our use of Cookies. 

Small pieces of data sent from a website and stored in the user’s web browser, commonly for technical purposes such as web analytics, are called cookies. We perform our web analytics mainly using Google Analytics, a Google, Inc. tool Advertising cookies allow advertisers to make ads more relevant to the user’s interests, but do not contain personally identifiable information, so users are still anonymous. Advertising cookies, sometimes referred to as third-party cookies, track navigation and publish ads on behalf of third parties.

More information about Google Analytics can be found in Google’s privacy policy: http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html.

The following are some examples of how we use cookies, including through services and partnerships with vendors and third party service providers:

  * Web analytics to capture demographic and other anonymous data for web optimization and other analysis; 
  * “Lead auditing” for ensuring accuracy, relevance and validity of information that is submitted; 
  * Tracking marketing and conversion, including, but not limited to, targeting and optimizing digital ad serving for improving relevance, user experience, and advertising effectiveness. 

Through your browser, you can remove cookies at any time. This may be required on a per use and not one time basis.

Also, you can generally opt-out of receiving personalized ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or those who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles, as well as from other third party advertisers and ad networks. You may unsubscribe by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA website.

### Contact Information

Our contact form may be used to address any questions or concerns about this Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.
